IUE-CWA Local 301; Records apap023
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
IUE-CWA Local 301 Records1939-2001
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried & Machine Workers, AFL-CIO. Local 301 (Schenectady, NY)
apap023
63.9 cubic ft. 7 reels of microfilm, 32 audio and video reels 854
Union founded at General Electric's Schenectady, NY plant after the passage of the Wagner Act.
Administrative History
Thomas Edison moved his Edison Machine Works to Schenectady, New York, in 1886 after a strike in New York City. Edison, however, was not successful in avoiding strikes and neither was the General Electric Company, which was formed by a merger of the Edison Electric Company and the Thomson-Houston Company. In 1904, for example, the 600 armature winders of the Schenectady General Electric Company held a 65-hour "folded arms" strike that was the first sit-down strike in the United States [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, p. 3]. The many craft unions at Schenectady General Electric called numerous strikes over the years leading to the organization of Local 301.
In 1926, the General Electric Company established a company union, the Works Council, at its Schenectady plant, and by the end of the 1920s all 36 of the craft unions previously representing workers at the plant had been eliminated [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, pp. 5-6]. During the Great Depression, General Electric took more liberties than usual with the rights of its workers, and the Works Council was ineffectual in answering the demands of workers. A small affiliate of the radical Trade Union Unity League formed in the Schenectady plant in 1932, and in the following year another small union was organized with many British socialists in its ranks. In 1934, these two unions merged into a single union of 300 members, and it was this union that was to become Local 301 in 1936 [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, pp. 9-10]. After the Wagner Act was passed in 1935 to guarantee workers' rights to organize, the Schenectady General Electric plant changed the Works Council to the Workers Council and removed management from the council in order to make the council a de facto union under the law [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, pp. 10-11]. After thousands of cards had been signed by the plant's workers, a National Labor Relations Board election was called between Local 301 of the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (UE) and the General Electric's Workers Council. On December 15, 1936, UE Local 301 became the collective bargaining agent for the plant's workers, defeating the company union by a vote of 5111 to 4033 [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, pp. 11-12].
After the successful election of UE Local 301 and the emergence of the UE and the CIO, the working conditions in the Schenectady plant and plants around the country began to improve. The first national contract with the General Electric Company was signed in 1938. Beginning in 1936, the union had struggled to provide women with equal pay for equal work, and in 1941 an agreement was negotiated with the company to attain this goal. In 1943 and 1944, job surveys were compiled of women's jobs, and many upgrades were put into effect, the second time by order of the War Labor Board. These upgrades worked to ensure that equal work was recognized as such by the company [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, pp. 16-18]. However, the company continued to break its stated rules for equal pay for years afterwards.
During World War II, the cost of living outstripped the raise in wages dramatically, but wages had been held down as part of the war effort. After failed negotiations for a pay raise in 1946, Local 301 initiated its first major strike. Over 20, 000 people took part in this strike, which was a success for Local 301 [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, pp. 19-20]. By the late 1940s, the union was faced with even more serious dilemmas. These were the years of anti-communism, and Local 301 and all of the UE had been under investigation by the U.S. government because of the alleged communist-domination of the union. This scrutiny led the CIO to expel the UE in 1949 and to replace it with the International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE) ["Labor Unions". In The Greenwood Encyclopedia of American Institutions. Gary M. Fink, ed. Westport, Conn. Greenwood Press, 1977]. In March 1954, the business manager of Local 301, Leo Jandreau, announced that Local 301, the largest remaining UE local, would join the IUE, and at an NLRB election following this announcement the local voted to do the same [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, p. 27].
During the period of 1956-1961, the union was confronted by a new GE vice-president of employee and public relations named Lemuel Boulware. Boulware established a bargaining strategy with Local 301 and other unions in which GE conducted research into the wages and working conditions of competitors and all of the unions' concerns and issues and put forth a "fair, firm offer" with nothing held back for future concessions. This bargaining strategy came to be known as "Boulwarism" and was roundly criticized by the labor unions, including Local 301, who described the practice as GE's attempt to ram concessions down the union members throats. After a nationwide strike in 1969 and various court decisions that went against General Electric, the company modified its approach the next year and Boulwarism began to fade as the preferred labor bargaining strategy [Joan Cook. "Lemuel Ricketts Boulware, 95; Headed Labor Relations for G.E".New York Times, 8 November 1990, p. B24].
In the 1960s, business interests in Schenectady developed the Make Schenectady Competitive Plan (MSC). The union fought against this plan, primarily because it would eliminate piece work earnings and result in lower wages for General Electric's employees. Schenectady General Electric said that if Local 301 did not sign the MSC agreement by October 1964, 5, 000 jobs would be transferred from that plant to another location, and the local signed a modified MSC plan by the company's deadline [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, pp. 33-34]. Two of the concessions the local won from the company were that 250 people would be hired each year for the next three years and that the company would soon begin a building program that would obviously lead to more jobs. The company failed to keep its promises, and on October 1, 1966, Local 301 went on strike. Two days later the strike was cancelled at the urging of President Lyndon B. Johnson, but on October 17 Local 301 was back on strike, along with the American Federation of Technical Employees, Local 147, Plumbers and Steamfitters, Local 128, and the small Teamsters local. The union was on strike for twelve weeks as both management and labor fought a propaganda war on television and in the newspapers. By the end of the strike, both sides made large concessions in order to come to an agreement [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, pp. 36-37].
During the next set of contract negotiations, the unions with members working at General Electric banded together in a technique known as coordinated bargaining. For the months of July, August and September of 1969, the unions met with management, but only the unions made proposals. General Electric was silent, a sign that the company was once again using Boulwarism as a "negotiating" technique. At the end of the negotiating, the company presented the unions with its first and final offer. On October 28, 1969, unions at General Electric plants across the country went on strike after rejecting the company's offer. The day after the strike began, the U.S. Court of Appeals handed down a decision that the company's practice of Boulwarism was illegal because it represented a refusal to bargain in good faith. This decision concerned an IUE suit from 1960, but this decision did not convince G.E. to change its tactics during this strike. The strike lasted more than fourteen weeks during the dead of winter, and thousands of Local 301 members were on the picket lines until a court order forced the local to reduce the number of picketers. Nationally, the strike ended and the contract was settled early in 1970, although the members of Local 301 voted 4-1 against the settlement [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, pp. 41-43].
As Local 301 moved into the 1970s and 1980s, the negotiating tactics of General Electric were forced to change, and strikes were nonexistent. In these decades, General Electric was forced to cut back the number of workers at its Schenectady plants and at other plants around the country. In Schenectady, G.E. has torn down many of its production buildings and layoffs have been massive. The membership of Local 301 has fallen from a high in the tens of thousands to just under one thousand today [Henry Antonelli and Helen Quirini. The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO: Reflections. Schenectady, N.Y., 1987, pp. 45-47].
Local 301 is currently known as IUE-CWA Local 301 as part of the Industrial Division of the Communication Workers of America.
Scope and Contents
The records of IUE Local 301 contain a significant amount of newspapers, memoranda, correspondence, subject files, audiotapes, and film.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized as follows:
Series 1: Officers and Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1969-1970, 1975-1985
Series 2: Membership Meeting Minutes, 1975-1985
Series 3: Subject Files, 1941-2001
Series 4: Audiovisual, ca. 1950-1976
Series 6: Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents, 1959-1985
Series 7: Photographs, 1948-1980s
Series 8: Grievance Files, 1959-1999
Series 9: Arbitration Files, 1960-1997
Organized into 9 file series by topic or format.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were lent to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by Local 301 of the International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers (IUE), and subsequently microfilmed as a part of the Harry Van Arsdale, Jr. Labor History Project in 1990. Some missing issues of Local 301 News were loaned for filming by Helen Quirini. The originals were returned to Local 301. An additional 85 cubic feet of material was acquired in February 2001 and 32 cubic feet of material was acquired in July 2004.
Related Materials
Related collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives can be found in the subject guide for Criminal Justice and Prisons.
Access
Access to segments of Series 6 is restricted. Access to the grievance files may also be restricted. Access to all other series in this record group is unrestricted.
Portions of the grievance files and arbitration files may be restricted. Contact a staff member for additional information.
Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Schenectady -- History -- 20th century.; Labor; Schenectady, New York; Digital Files; International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine & Furniture Workers (Local 301); General Electric Company.
- Officers and Executive Board Meeting Minutes (microfilmed), 1969-1970; 1
  - Minutes, 1969 (Reel 1)
  - Minutes, 1970 (Reel 1)
  - Minutes, 1975 (Reel 1)
  - Minutes, 1976 (Reel 1)
  - Minutes, 1977 (Reel 1)
  - Minutes, 1978 (Reel 1)
  - Minutes, 1979 (Reel 1)
  - Minutes, 1980 January-1980 June (Reel 2)
  - Minutes, 1980 July-1980 December (Reel 2)
  - Minutes, 1981 (Reel 2)
  - Minutes, 1982 (Reel 2)
  - Minutes, 1983 (Reel 2)
  - Minutes, 1984 (Reel 2)
  - Minutes, 1985 (Reel 2)
- Membership Meeting Minutes (microfilmed), 1975-1985; 2
  - Minutes, 1975 (Reel 3)
  - Minutes, 1976 (Reel 3)
  - Minutes, 1977 (Reel 3)
  - Minutes, 1978 (Reel 3)
  - Minutes, 1979 (Reel 3)
  - Minutes, 1980 (Reel 3)
  - Minutes, 1981 (Reel 3)
  - Minutes, 1982 (Reel 3)
  - Minutes, 1983 (Reel 3)
  - Minutes, 1984 (Reel 3)
  - Minutes, 1985 (Reel 3)
- Subject Files, 1941-2001; 3
  Scope and Contents
  Series 3 contains correspondence, memos, pamphlets, receipts, and related materials concerning the union, GE, and community issues. The series contains material related to the financial organization of the union and to the strikes of the 1940s, 1960s, and 1980s as well. All strike materials are located in this series with some exceptions. News clippings appear in this series, while full newspapers of are found in Series 5.
  Note: Microfilm reels in Series 3 and Audiovisual Series 4 also contain information related to the strikes, some of which is not duplicated in the file folders. Series 3 is also composed of both reels and file folders as noted in the box and folder list. (For all subject files, no subject is documented completely).
  - Anniversary Book for Local 301's Fiftieth Anniversary, 1986 (Reel 1)
  - Bulletins and Notices, 1981-1982 (Reel 1)
  - Bulletins and Notices, 1979-1980 (Reel 1)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1959; 1978 (Reel 1)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws of IUE and IUE District Council 3, 1949; 1954; 1959; 1965; 1979 (Reel 1)
  - Constitution Committee, 1958-1959 (Reel 1)
  - Contract Benefit Manuals, 1970; 1973 (Reel 1)
  - Contract Negotiations, 1969-1973 (Reel 1)
  - Coordinated Bargaining Committee--General Electric and Westinghouse Unions, 1969 (Reel 1)
  - Coordinated Bargaining Committee--General Electric and Westinghouse Unions, 1973 (Reel 1)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Reel 1)
  - Correspondence to Editor of Schenectady Gazette, 1969; 1974 (Reel 1)
  - Dual Unionism, ca. 1971 (Reel 1)
  - Education Committee--Photograph, 1979 (Reel 1)
  - Employee Benefits Manual, 1966 (Reel 1)
  - The Local 301 Story, 1968 (Reel 2)
  - National Labor Relations Board Election Between IUE and UE, 1951 (Reel 2)
  - Power Efficiency Program, 1985 (Reel 2)
  - Press Releases, 1967-1971 (Reel 2)
  - Press Releases, 1972-1978 (Reel 2)
  - Retirees Club Meeting Minutes, 1972-1983 (Reel 2)
  - Schenectady Area Industrial Unions Council--Photograph, ca. 1955 (Reel 2)
  - Schenectady Industrial Development Council (formerly GUTS), 1960-1961 (Reel 2)
  - Shambo, John, ca. 1970 (Reel 2)
  - The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO, 1987 (Reel 2)
  - Teachers' Strike, ca. 1975 (Reel 2)
  - Testimony Before the McCarthy Senate Committee on Unemployment, 1960 (Reel 2)
  - Strikes, Photographs, 1966; 1969 (Reel 2)
  - UE Factsheets, 1960 (Reel 2)
  - Accounting, Miscellaneous, 1966-1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Appeals, J. Rosamino Appeal on election results - (Also contains: 3 cassettes on J. Rosamino)., 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Appeals, Serafin Pita Appeal on elections, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Appeals, Sibby Rebaldo, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Appeals and Complaints, 1976-1979 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Attorney, Anthony Pisano, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Audit Committee, General Files, 1958-1980 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Audit Files, Central Labor Council, Exchanges, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Audit Files, Charitable Donations, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Audit Files, Compensation Insurance, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Audit Files, Computer Data, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Audit Files, COPE, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Audit Files, Disability Insurance, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Audit Files, District 3, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Audit Files, Employees Assistance Program Billings, 1982-1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Audit Files, Employees Assistance Program Exchange Accounting, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Audit Files, Energy Committee, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Audit Files, Exchanges, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Banking, 1967-1971 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Banking, Investments, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Benefits, 1960-1980 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Bonds, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Bonds, Better Neighborhood Bond, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Bonds, Blanket Bond Coverage, 1960-1975; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Business Agent, Dante DeCesare - (Contains: Business files associated with Dante DeCesare, correspondence, news items, memos)., 1980-1982 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Business Agent, Joseph Mangino - (Contains: Business files associated with Joseph Mangino, correspondence, news items, memos)., 1969-1979 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Central Labor Exchange, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Charities and Invitations, 1978-1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Conferences and Conventions, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Constitution and By-laws 1959-1978, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Constitutional Convention, 11th AFL/CIO, 1968 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Constitutional Convention, 12th AFL/CIO, 1969 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Constitutions, Central Labor Council, AFL/CIO Constitution and By-laws, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Constitutions, IUE International and District 3 Constitutions, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - COPE, 1967-1970 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Correspondence - (Contains: correspondence of John Shambo, Leo Jandreau, Joseph Drozdowski, Angelo Durante; deals with workmen's compensation, treasury, letter to Sen. Jacob K. Javits)., 1960-1971 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Correspondence - (Contains: letters of Angelo Durante, Joseph Mangino; deals with meeting announcements, mailing lists, etc.)., 1973-1981 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - (Contains: building standards, verification of employment, etc.)., 1982-1984; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Cuomo, Mario, Endorsement for Governor of New York, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Delegates, District 3, 1978-1980 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Department of Labor, 1984 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Directory, Senior Citizens Clubs and Centers, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Dues, 1970-1984 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Dues, Vacation Dues Owed, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Employees Assistance Program, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Employees Assistance Program, Expenses, 1984 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Election - (Contains: ballots, election notices, memos, correspondence, news clippings, notes)., 1961-1979 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Election - (Contains: ballots, election notices, memos, correspondence, news clippings, notes)., 1980-1982 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Election - (Contains: ballots, election notices, memos, correspondence, notes)., Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Election, Officers, 1967-1985 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Employment Report, Monthly, 1956-1966 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - EUH Deposits, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Finances - (Contains: statistical reports, memos, correspondence, notes)., 1964-1969 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Financial Report, Special, 1981 February 14 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Financial Reports, 1975-1979 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Financial Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Financial Reports, 1982 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Financial Reports, 1984 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Grievances, 1959-1975 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Health Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Histories, Oral History, Interview of AC Stevens, 1991 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Histories, Oral History of Local 301, Interview of Joseph Mangino, 1998 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Histories, Oral History of Local 301, Joseph Mangino, 1999-2001 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Histories and Fact Sheets of Local 301 and UE, ca. 1970s; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Income and Expenses Statements, 1961-1979 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Insurance, 1966-1984 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Insurance, James Villano File, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Inventory, 1971-1972 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Job Hunter's Directories, 1980 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Knolls Atomic Power Laboratory - (includes: local supplemental agreements, KAPL Bulletins, news related documents)., 1962-1969 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Labor Service, Volume 2, Prentice Hall - (Contains: detailed information on labor regulations, national organization policy)., 1941 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Legal Cases, 1970-1984; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Legal Expenses, 1984 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Lost Time Vouchers and Receipts, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Map, General Electric's Schenectady Plant, Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Memos - (Contains: memos on special meetings, important bulletins, updates, etc.)., 1960-1970 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Minutes of Meetings, 1956-1977 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1960-1979; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Mission to Southeast Asia, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Names, Addresses, Phone Number Listings, 1961-1980s; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - New York State Energy Plan, Vol. I, 1994 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - New York State Energy Plan, Vol. II, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - New York State Energy Plan, Vol. III, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - News and Newspapers, Miscellaneous - (includes: Electrical Union News, Rank-and-File Voice, AFL-CIO News Service)., 1953-1982 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Pension Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Pension Policy, 1973-1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Pensioner's Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Posters, Meetings of Members and Shop Stewards, 1975-1984 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Profit Sharing, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Profit Sharing Guide, 1965 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Raffle, 1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Receipts, 1965-1979 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Recreation, 1965-1983 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Recreation, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Register of Reporting Labor Organizations, 1960-1962 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Repairs, Build. Comm. Repairs, 1969 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)